Tufts New England Medical Center Planning Office Records UA014
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
- Publications, 1940 -- 1981; 1943 -- 1971; UA014.004; 3.6 Linear Feet
  - Clinic Operation Survey Report, Tufts University School of Dental Medicine, 1970; UA014.004.014.00034 (Box 14)
  - Cost-Benefit Analysis, TNEMC Planning Office, 1970; UA014.004.014.00035 (Box 14)
  - Coupling Mental Health Services into the Community General Hospital System, TNEMC Planning Office, 1967; UA014.004.014.00036 (Box 14)
  - Dental Health Sciences Building, TNEMC, 1973; UA014.004.014.00037 (Box 14)
  - Dental Instrument Processing Facilities Study for University of Minnesota H.S.C., The Architects Collaborative, Inc., 1970; UA014.004.014.00038 (Box 14)
  - Development of Tufts-New England Medical Center 1965-1985: A Preliminary Study, TNEMC Planning Office, 1964; UA014.004.014.00039 (Box 14)
  - Frances Stern Nutrition Center-Masters Program, TNEMC, 1975; UA014.004.014.00040 (Box 14)
  - Health Facilities Research, The Hospitals and Health Committee of the New York Chapter of the American Institute of Architects, 1970; UA014.004.014.00041 (Box 14)
  - The Health Fund for Medical Care Education and Research, Richard A. Ehrlich, TNEMC, 1964; UA014.004.014.00042 (Box 14)
  - Hospital Planning Document: Volume One - Context, TNEMC Planning Office, 1970; UA014.004.014.00043 (Box 14)
  - Hospital Planning Document: Volume Two - Adult Programs, TNEMC Planning Office, 1970; UA014.004.014.00044 (Box 14)
  - Hospital Planning Document: Volume Three - Pediatric Programs, TNEMC Planning Office, 1969; UA014.004.014.00045 (Box 14)
  - Hospital Planning Document: Volume Four - Non-Medical Programs, TNEMC Planning Office, 1970; UA014.004.014.00046 (Box 14)
  - Hospital Planning Document: Volume Five - Supply and Services, TNEMC Planning Office, 1969; UA014.004.014.00047 (Box 14)
  - Hospital Planning Document: Volume Six - Planning Directives, TNEMC Planning Office, 1970; UA014.004.014.00048 (Box 14)
  - Hospital Planning Document: Volume Seven - Appendices, TNEMC Planning Office, 1970; UA014.004.014.00049 (Box 14)
  - How Tufts Tackles the Problem of Better Medical Care for New England, Tufts College Medical School Develpment Program, 1940; UA014.004.014.00050 (Box 14)
  - Industrial Engineering Report, New England Medical Center Hospitals, Chas. T. Main Engineers, 1967; UA014.004.015.00001 (Box 15)
  - Inpatient Admission Survey Report, New England Center Hospital Survey, TNEMC Planning Office, 1969; UA014.004.015.00002 (Box 15)
  - Married Student Housing at the Tufts-New England Medical Center, TNEMC Planning Office, 1964; UA014.004.015.00003 (Box 15)
  - Married Student Housing at the Tufts-New England Medical Center 1965-1975, TNEMC Planning Office, 1966; UA014.004.015.00004 (Box 15)
  - Mechanisms of Regulation of Growth, Report of the Fortieth Ross Conference on Pediatric Research, Ross Laboratories, 1962; UA014.004.015.00005 (Box 15)
  - Medical Rehabilitation Research and Training Center Number Seven Annual Progress Report, Office of Human Develpment Rehabilitation Services Administration, 1977; UA014.004.015.00006 (Box 15)
  - Medical School and Teaching Hospitals: Curriculum, Programming and Planning, Annals of the New York Academy of Sciences Vol 128 Art 2, 1965; UA014.004.015.00007 (Box 15)
  - Mental Health Coupling Project Grant Proposal, TNEMC Planning Office, 1969; UA014.004.015.00008 (Box 15)
  - Mental Health Coupling Project Interim Report, TNEMC Planning Office, 1968; UA014.004.015.00009 (Box 15)
  - New England Medical Center Hospitals Phase 1-A, TNEMC Planning Office, 1955; UA014.004.015.00010 (Box 15)
  - New England Medical Center in the South Cove, Submitted to the Executive Board of NEMC by Kevin Lynch, Planning Consultant, 1955; UA014.004.015.00011 (Box 15)
  - Parking Study for Tufts University and New England Medical Center, Richard C. Rich and Associates, 1965; UA014.004.015.00012 (Box 15)
  - Preliminary Architectural Program for the Proposed Medical Education Building, Tufts University School of Medicine, TNEMC Planning Office, 1969; UA014.004.015.00013 (Box 15)
  - Problems of Pediatric Hospital Design, Tufts University School of Medicine, Marshall Kreidberg, Hermann Field et al., TNEMC Planning Office, 1965; UA014.004.015.00014 (Box 15)
  - Proposal of Dental Clinical Instrument Processing Facilities, Tufts University School of Dental Medicine, 1970; UA014.004.015.00015 (Box 15)
  - A Proposal for a New Program in Medical Education at Tufts University Medical School, The Faculty Medical Education Group, 1968; UA014.004.015.00016 (Box 15)
  - A Proposal for a New Program in Medical Education at Tufts University Medical School, The Student Medical Education Group, 1968; UA014.004.015.00017 (Box 15)
  - Proposed Property Adjustments and Development Needs: 1965-1985, TNEMC Planning Office, 1964; UA014.004.015.00018 (Box 15)
  - Properties Within Medical Center Development Area, TNEMC Planning Office, 1965; UA014.004.015.00019 (Box 15)
  - Property Adjustment and Development Needs: 1965-1985, TNEMC Planning Office, 1964; UA014.004.015.00020 (Box 15)
  - Property Status and Unit Ownership, TNEMC Planning Office, 1964; UA014.004.015.00021 (Box 15)
  - The Quincy School Project Final Report Year One, Boston School Department and TNEMC, Frank W. Kibbe, Jr., 1967; UA014.004.015.00022 (Box 15)
  - A Regional Medical Education Program for Tufts-New England Medical Center, Leon Shapiro and Katherine Oppermann, TNEMC, 1972; UA014.004.015.00023 (Box 15)
  - Report of the Boston Floating Hospital, TNEMC, 1951; UA014.004.015.00024 (Box 15)
  - Report on Housing Demand at TNEMC, TNEMC Planning Office, 1970; UA014.004.015.00025 (Box 15)
  - Report on Recreation Facilities, TNEMC Planning Office, 1967; UA014.004.015.00026 (Box 15)
  - Some Values Accruing to the Use of the St. James Site for the Logistics Center, TNEMC Planning Office, 1969; UA014.004.015.00027 (Box 15)
  - A Tradition of Helping, The Boston Dispensary, UA014.004.015.00028 (Box 15)
  - T-NEMC Master Plan Report, The Architects Collaborative Inc., 1970; UA014.004.015.00029 (Box 15)
  - Tufts Survey of Dental Practice, Biodental Engineering Research Project, 1970; UA014.004.015.00030 (Box 15)
  - Welcome: A Patient's Guide, New England Medical Center, 1981; UA014.004.015.00031 (Box 15)
- Oversize, UA014.005; 0.0 Linear Feet
  The Oversize series includes five oversize plans that were moved from the subject files series to be stored in the map case. Cross-references were put into the original folders to alert users to the new location.
  This series contains one folder.
  - Oversize T-NEMC, UA014.005.016.00001 (Box 16)
    Complete titles of these items are as follows: T-NEMC South Cove Property Status and Unit Ownership; Illustrative Sight Plan Washington Park Urban Renewal Area, Boston Redevelopment Authority; Garage-Laboratory, New England Medical Center Development Program.
- Subject files, 1932 -- 1980; 1960 -- 1971; UA014.006; 13.2 Linear Feet
  This series contains administrative records, reports and documentation, including some correspondence and visual materials, created by the T-NEMC Planning Office relating to the development of the Medical Center and its surrounding area. Includes agendas and minutes from the meetings of various committees. Architectural records include plans, studies and proposals and other documents. Also included are documents regarding T-NEMC's involvement with the Boston Redevelopment Authority (BRA), the Quincy School Project (QSP) and the renewal of South Cove and Chinatown. Additionally, this series contains administrative files pertaining to T-NEMC units, such as pediatric and dental care.
  This series is arranged alphabetically. Committee folders are arranged alphabetically and then chronological within each committee.
  - Act Relating to Compositon, Powers, Status at NEMC, 1960 -- 1970; UA014.006.001.00001 (Box 1)
  - Alternative Stragies: Basic Science Facilitices, 1969; UA014.006.001.00002 (Box 1)
  - Alternative Strategies for Development of Basic Science Facilities, 1969; UA014.006.001.00003 (Box 1)
  - Amirault, Genevieve, R.N. Director of Nursing- BFH, 1960; UA014.006.001.00004 (Box 1)
  - Andover Planning Conference Report, 1967; UA014.006.001.00005 (Box 1)
  - Andover Planning Conference Workbook, 1967; UA014.006.001.00006 (Box 1)
  - Andover Planning Conference, 1968; UA014.006.001.00007 (Box 1)
  - Andover Planning Conference, 1968; UA014.006.001.00008 (Box 1)
  - Andover Planning Conference, 1969; UA014.006.001.00009 (Box 1)
  - Andover Planning Conference deBurlo, 1969; UA014.006.001.00010 (Box 1)
  - Angoff, Kristine Play Teacher, 1962; UA014.006.001.00011 (Box 1)
  - Application for Grant For Teaching Facilities Construction, 1969; UA014.006.001.00012 (Box 1)
  - Applications, 1968; UA014.006.001.00013 (Box 1)
  - Architect Selections, 1964; UA014.006.001.00014 (Box 1)
  - Architectual Programs Draft NEMC Hospitals, 1967; UA014.006.001.00015 (Box 1)
  - Boston Redevelopment Authority, 112 Credits, 1963; UA014.006.001.00016 (Box 1)
  - Boston Redevelopment Authority, Cooperation Agreements City, BRA and T-NEMC, 1962; UA014.006.001.00017 (Box 1)
  - Boston Redevelopment Authority, Development, Adminis., Edward J. Logue, 1960; UA014.006.001.00018 (Box 1)
  - Boston Redevelopment Authority, General, 1962; UA014.006.001.00019 (Box 1)
  - Boston Redevelopment Authority, Housing Policy, 1962; UA014.006.001.00020 (Box 1)
  - Boston Redevelopment Authority, Institutions, B.U. Medical Center, 1961; UA014.006.001.00021 (Box 1)
  - Boston Redevelopment Authority, Institutions, Hospitals, 1958 -- 1960; UA014.006.001.00022 (Box 1)
  - Boston Redevelopment Authority, Institutions, Mayor's College Com., 1960 -- 1962; UA014.006.001.00023 (Box 1)
  - Boston Redevelopment Authority, Maps, UA014.006.001.00024 (Box 1)
  - Boston Redevelopment Authority, New York Streets, 1955 -- 1959; UA014.006.001.00025 (Box 1)
  - Boston Redevelopment Authority, Sargent School Survey, South Cove Schools, 1962; UA014.006.001.00026 (Box 1)
  - Boston Redevelopment Authority, Section 112, Folder 1, 1960 -- 1963; UA014.006.001.00027 (Box 1)
  - Boston Redevelopment Authority, Section 112, Folder 2, 1960 -- 1963; UA014.006.001.00028 (Box 1)
  - Boston Redevelopment Authority, Section 112, Institutions Committee, 1961; UA014.006.001.00029 (Box 1)
  - Boston Redevelopment Authority, Section 112, T-NEMC Credits, 1961 -- 1963; UA014.006.001.00030 (Box 1)
  - Boston Redevelopment Authority, Section 112, Tax Information, 1932 -- 1963; UA014.006.001.00031 (Box 1)
  - Boston Redevelopment Authority, Service Payments, 1962; UA014.006.001.00032 (Box 1)
  - Boston Redevelopment Authority, Skid Row, 1962; UA014.006.001.00033 (Box 1)
  - Boston Redevelopment Authority, South Cove, Developers, 1962; UA014.006.001.00034 (Box 1)
  - Boston Redevelopment Authority, South Cove, M.T.A., 1962; UA014.006.001.00035 (Box 1)
  - Boston Redevelopment Authority, South Cove, Past Plans, UA014.006.001.00036 (Box 1)
  - Boston Redevelopment Authority, South Cove Project, 1965; UA014.006.001.00037 (Box 1)
  - Boston Redevelopment Authority, South Cove, S&P Application, 1962; UA014.006.001.00038 (Box 1)
  - Boston Redevelopment Authority, South Cove, S&P Application: Acquisitions-Turnpike, UA014.006.001.00039 (Box 1)
  - Boston Redevelopment Authority, South Cove, S&P Application: Block Data (Empty Folder), UA014.006.001.00040 (Box 1)
  - Boston Redevelopment Authority, South Cove, S&P Application: Census Data, UA014.006.001.00041 (Box 1)
  - Boston Redevelopment Authority, South Cove, S&P Application: Land Area Data, UA014.006.001.00042 (Box 1)
  - Boston Redevelopment Authority, South Cove, S&P Application: Project Expenditures, 1961; UA014.006.001.00043 (Box 1)
  - Boston Redevelopment Authority, South Cove, S&P Application: South Cove Maps, 1960; UA014.006.001.00044 (Box 1)
  - Boston Redevelopment Authority, South Cove, T-NEMC Relations, 1960 -- 1962; UA014.006.001.00045 (Box 1)
  - Boston Redevelopment Authority, South Cove, Tax Portrait, UA014.006.001.00046 (Box Large Map Case 1 Drawer 7)
    Oversize "B.R.A. South Cove Tax Portrait" was pulled. No Date Available.
  - Boston Redevelopment Authority, South Cove, Urban Design, UA014.006.001.00047 (Box 1)
  - Boston Redevelopment Authority, South Cove, Urban Renewal Plan, 1962; UA014.006.001.00048 (Box 1)
  - Boston Redevelopment Authority, South End, 1961 -- 1965; UA014.006.001.00049 (Box 1)
  - Boston Redevelopment Authority, South End, Castle Square, 1962; UA014.006.001.00050 (Box 1)
  - Boston Redevelopment Authority, South End, Preliminary Plan, 1962 -- 1964; UA014.006.001.00051 (Box 1)
  - Boston Redevelopment Authority, South End, Urban Renewal Committee, 1963; UA014.006.001.00052 (Box 1)
  - B.R.A. statistics, development, etc., 1960 -- 1975; UA014.006.002.00001 (Box 2)
  - B.R.A. survey forms, UA014.006.002.00002 (Box 2)
  - B.R.A. T-NEMC development plan, UA014.006.002.00003 (Box 2)
  - B.R.A. Transportation, Massachusetts Turnpike Authority, 1962; UA014.006.002.00004 (Box 2)
  - B.R.A. Urban Renewal Report, Greater Boston Chamber of Commerce, 1963; UA014.006.002.00005 (Box 2)
  - B.R.A. Washington Park, 1960 -- 1963; UA014.006.002.00006 (Box 2)
    Oversize "B.R.A. Washington Park" was pulled, see UA014.005.016.00001.
  - B.R.A. Waterfront, 1961 -- 1962; UA014.006.002.00007 (Box 2)
  - B.R.A. West End Project Plan, 1955 -- 1959; UA014.006.002.00008 (Box 2)
  - B.R.A. Zoning Code, 1962; UA014.006.002.00009 (Box 2)
  - Baty, James Marvin, M.D., Pediatrician-in-Chief, 1962; UA014.006.002.00010 (Box 2)
  - Biodental engineering, 1964 -- 1970; UA014.006.002.00011 (Box 2)
  - Biodental engineering 2, 1965 -- 1969; UA014.006.002.00012 (Box 2)
  - Biodental engineering grant, 1966; UA014.006.002.00013 (Box 2)
  - Biodental engineering study, group minutes to meetings, 1965 -- 1967; UA014.006.002.00014 (Box 2)
  - Bogen, H., Role of NEMC in city of Boston, 1959; UA014.006.002.00015 (Box 2)
  - Boston City Council, 1963; UA014.006.002.00016 (Box 2)
  - Boston Columbia Point, 1966; UA014.006.002.00017 (Box 2)
  - Boston Dispensary Rehabilitation Institute, Comparative Statistical Graphs, 1963; UA014.006.002.00018 (Box 2)
  - Boston Floating Hospital Evaluation Conference on USPH Grant # 0235, "Study new design concepts for a children's hospital", 1964; UA014.006.002.00019 (Box 2)
  - Boston Floating Hospital Report, UA014.006.002.00020 (Box 2)
  - Boston Redevelopment Authority, 1970; UA014.006.002.00021 (Box 2)
  - Central Services Unit Program, UA014.006.002.00022 (Box 2)
  - Chinese-American Civic Association News, 1967 -- 1969; UA014.006.002.00023 (Box 2)
  - Chinese Community Center, 1970 -- 1972; UA014.006.002.00024 (Box 2)
  - Chinese Community, Free Chinatown committee, 1971; UA014.006.002.00025 (Box 2)
  - Citizen Advisory Committee, 1965 -- 1966; UA014.006.002.00026 (Box 2)
  - Columbia Point, UA014.006.002.00027 (Box 2)
  - Committee, Executive, 1961 -- 1965; UA014.006.002.00028 (Box 2)
  - Committee, Fund-raising, 1961 -- 1964; UA014.006.002.00029 (Box 2)
  - Committee, Hospital Planning, H.H.F. Additional Memoranda, 1965 -- 1966; UA014.006.002.00030 (Box 2)
  - Committee, Hospital Planning Minutes, 1965 -- 1966; UA014.006.002.00031 (Box 2)
  - Committee, Hospital Planning, 1967; UA014.006.002.00032 (Box 2)
  - Committee, Joint Planning, Falmouth Conference, Mr. H. Fields, 1966; UA014.006.002.00033 (Box 2)
  - Committee, Joint Planning: Minutes, 1966 -- 1967; UA014.006.003.00001 (Box 3)
  - Committee, Joint Planning, 1967; UA014.006.003.00002 (Box 3)
  - Committee, Joint Planning: Minutes I, 1967; UA014.006.003.00003 (Box 3)
  - Committee, Joint Planning: Suggested Program for T-NEMC Inc., 1967; UA014.006.003.00004 (Box 3)
  - Committee, Joint Planning: Book I, 1968; UA014.006.003.00005 (Box 3)
  - Committee, Joint Planning: Book II, 1968; UA014.006.003.00006 (Box 3)
  - Committee, Joint Planning: Minutes I, 1968; UA014.006.003.00007 (Box 3)
  - Committee, Objectives: Clarification of Assumptions, 1964; UA014.006.003.00008 (Box 3)
  - Committee, Objectives: H.H. Fields, 1961 -- 1964; UA014.006.003.00009 (Box 3)
  - Committee, Objectives, 1962 -- 1965; UA014.006.003.00010 (Box 3)
  - Committee, Objectives, 1964; UA014.006.003.00011 (Box 3)
  - Committee, Planning, 1968; UA014.006.003.00012 (Box 3)
  - Committee, Planning: Book II, 1969; UA014.006.003.00013 (Box 3)
  - Committee, Planning: Meeting #9, Minutes, 1969; UA014.006.003.00014 (Box 3)
  - Committee, Planning: New England Medical Center Hospitals, Report Phase 1-B, 1971; UA014.006.003.00015 (Box 3)
  - Committee, Planning and Construction: Minutes, 1965 -- 1966; UA014.006.003.00016 (Box 3)
  - Committee, Special Committee on Organization, 1963; UA014.006.003.00017 (Box 3)
  - Committee, University Planning #1: Minutes, Memos, and Notes, 1965 -- 1966; UA014.006.003.00018 (Box 3)
  - Committee, Working: Patient, 1962 -- 1963; UA014.006.003.00019 (Box 3)
  - Committee, Working: Basic Sciences, 1962 -- 1963; UA014.006.003.00020 (Box 3)
  - Committee, Working: Organization, 1963; UA014.006.003.00021 (Box 3)
  - Community Health, 1960 -- 1968; UA014.006.004.00001 (Box 4)
  - Communications Study - Planning Office Copy, Folder 1, 1960 -- 1963; UA014.006.004.00002 (Box 4)
  - Communications Study - Planning Office Copy, Folder 2, 1963; UA014.006.004.00003 (Box 4)
  - Conference Memorandums, 1960 -- 1962; UA014.006.004.00004 (Box 4)
  - Conference Room Schedules, 1966 -- 1967; UA014.006.004.00005 (Box 4)
  - Confidential Reports, Book II, 1965 -- 1966; UA014.006.004.00006 (Box 4)
  - Confidential Reports, Book II, 1967 -- 1968; UA014.006.004.00007 (Box 4)
  - Confidential Reports, Book III, 1962 -- 1970; UA014.006.004.00008 (Box 4)
  - Consultants Reports, 1968; UA014.006.004.00009 (Box 4)
  - Context, 1962 -- 1980; UA014.006.004.00010 (Box 4)
  - Cost-Benefit Analysis: Medical Education Building, 1970 -- 1972; UA014.006.004.00011 (Box 4)
  - Demonstration/Experimental Research Reports, 1967 -- 1969; UA014.006.004.00012 (Box 4)
  - Dental Clinic Utilization Survey, 1967 -- 1970; UA014.006.004.00013 (Box 4)
  - Dental School Personnel Graphs, 1964; UA014.006.004.00014 (Box 4)
  - Departments Planning Office: Problems of Pediatric Design, 1966 -- 1967; UA014.006.004.00015 (Box 4)
  - Diagrams: Patient Care, UA014.006.004.00016 (Box 4)
  - The Ecology of Boston Floating Hospital - Kramer, 1964; UA014.006.004.00017 (Box 4)
  - Education Facilities: Diagrams, UA014.006.004.00018 (Box 4)
  - Elements of Projected T-NEMC, 1963; UA014.006.005.00001 (Box 5)
  - Elevators, 1969; UA014.006.005.00002 (Box 5)
  - Engineering Proposal - Chas T. Main, Inc., 1969; UA014.006.005.00003 (Box 5)
  - Europe Report, 1962; UA014.006.005.00004 (Box 5)
  - Executive Administrator's Confidential Report, 1967 -- 1969; UA014.006.005.00005 (Box 5)
  - Experimental In-Patient Facility, 1966 -- 1967; UA014.006.005.00006 (Box 5)
  - Fisher, John H., MD, Ped. Surgeon-in-Chief, 1963; UA014.006.005.00007 (Box 5)
  - Floating Hospital, UA014.006.005.00008 (Box 5)
  - Floating Hospital I-B, 1962 -- 1972; UA014.006.005.00009 (Box 5)
  - Floating Hospital, General, 1961 -- 1966; UA014.006.005.00010 (Box 5)
  - Floating Hospital, History of, 1957; UA014.006.005.00011 (Box 5)
  - Grant Application for Construction of Teaching Facilities, 1969; UA014.006.005.00012 (Box 5)
  - Grant Application: Original, 1967 -- 1969; UA014.006.005.00013 (Box 5)
  - Graphics of Sample Study - Patient Population, 1963; UA014.006.005.00014 (Box 5)
  - "Health in the Troubled Cities," Lowell Lecture Series, 1968; UA014.006.005.00015 (Box 5)
  - Hill-Boston Application, 1963; UA014.006.005.00016 (Box 5)
  - Hospital I-A: Programming, 1966 -- 1969; UA014.006.005.00017 (Box 5)
  - Hospital Dept. Reports, 1968; UA014.006.005.00018 (Box 5)
  - Hospital Planning: Internal Memoranda, 1965 -- 1966; UA014.006.005.00019 (Box 5)
  - Hospital Planning: General, 1967; UA014.006.005.00020 (Box 5)
  - Hospitals: Massachusetts NEMCH Hospitals, 1965; UA014.006.005.00021 (Box 5)
  - Hospitals: Mental Health - D. Kennedy Paper, 1965; UA014.006.005.00022 (Box 5)
  - Hospitals: Nursing - R.T. Viguers Ohio Paper, 1967; UA014.006.005.00023 (Box 5)
  - Hospitals: Pediatric Design, 1962; UA014.006.005.00024 (Box 5)
  - Hospitals: Planning, 1968; UA014.006.005.00025 (Box 5)
  - Housing Cost Analysis, 1961; UA014.006.005.00026 (Box 5)
  - Housing - Sheltered, 1970 -- 1975; UA014.006.005.00027 (Box 5)
  - Initial Overview Task Force #21, 1967; UA014.006.005.00028 (Box 5)
  - Intramural Practice, 1968; UA014.006.005.00029 (Box 5)
  - Joint Medical School Hospital Site Visit, 1965 -- 1969; UA014.006.005.00030 (Box 5)
  - Land, Building, Space Inventory: Animal Farm, 1962; UA014.006.005.00031 (Box 5)
  - Land, Building, Space Inventory: Adjunct Diag & Therapeutic Services, 1962; UA014.006.005.00032 (Box 5)
  - Land, Building, Space Inventory: Adult Bed Facilities, 1962; UA014.006.005.00033 (Box 5)
  - Land, Building, Space Inventory: Basic Science Department, 1962; UA014.006.005.00034 (Box 5)
  - Land, Building, Space Inventory: Communications, 1962; UA014.006.005.00035 (Box 5)
  - Land, Building, Space Inventory: Central School Functions, 1962; UA014.006.005.00036 (Box 5)
  - Land, Building, Space Inventory: Central Stores & Supplies, 1962; UA014.006.005.00037 (Box 5)
  - Land, Building, Space Inventory: Dental Clinical Department & Clinics, 1962; UA014.006.005.00038 (Box 5)
  - Land, Building, Space Inventory: Dental School Administration, 1962; UA014.006.005.00039 (Box 5)
  - Land, Building, Space Inventory: Dining Facilities, 1962; UA014.006.005.00040 (Box 5)
  - Land, Building, Space Inventory: Educational Technology, 1962; UA014.006.005.00041 (Box 5)
  - Land, Building, Space Inventory: Employee Facilities, 1962; UA014.006.005.00042 (Box 5)
  - Land, Building, Space Inventory: Hospital Administration, 1962; UA014.006.005.00043 (Box 5)
  - Land, Building, Space Inventory: Hospital Educational Facilities, 1962; UA014.006.005.00044 (Box 5)
  - Land, Building, Space Inventory: Library, 1962; UA014.006.005.00045 (Box 5)
  - Land, Building, Space Inventory: Maintenance & Mechanical, 1962; UA014.006.005.00046 (Box 5)
  - Land, Building, Space Inventory: Medical School Administration, 1962; UA014.006.005.00047 (Box 5)
  - Land, Building, Space Inventory: Nursing Education, 1962; UA014.006.005.00048 (Box 5)
  - Land, Building, Space Inventory: O.P.D. Clinics, 1962; UA014.006.005.00049 (Box 5)
  - Land, Building, Space Inventory: Other Educational Prog. - Bingham Assoc., 1962; UA014.006.005.00050 (Box 5)
  - Land, Building, Space Inventory: School of Occupational Therapy, 1962; UA014.006.005.00051 (Box 5)
  - Land, Building, Space Inventory: Paediatric Bed Facilities, 1962; UA014.006.005.00052 (Box 5)
  - Land, Building, Space Inventory: Public Facilities, 1962; UA014.006.005.00053 (Box 5)
  - Land, Building, Space Inventory: Service Department - Hospital, 1962; UA014.006.005.00054 (Box 5)
  - Land, Building, Space Inventory: Student Dormitories, 1962; UA014.006.005.00055 (Box 5)
  - Land, Building, Space Inventory: T-NEMC Administration, 1962; UA014.006.005.00056 (Box 5)
  - Land, Building, Space Inventory: Vacant Space, 1962; UA014.006.005.00057 (Box 5)
  - Land, Building, Space Inventory: Volunteer Services, 1962; UA014.006.005.00058 (Box 5)
  - Land, Building, Space Inventory: T-NEMC, 1962; UA014.006.005.00059 (Box 5)
  - Land Building Space Study; Study of Existing Facilities, 1962; UA014.006.006.00001 (Box 6)
  - Card Cost Studies, 1966 -- 1969; UA014.006.006.00002 (Box 6)
  - Land - Space Survey Draft II, 1962; UA014.006.006.00003 (Box 6)
  - Levis Report, 112 Credits, 1962 -- 1963; UA014.006.006.00004 (Box 6)
  - Logistics Center, Medical Records, 1965 -- 1968; UA014.006.006.00005 (Box 6)
  - Long Range Planning, 1969 -- 1972; UA014.006.006.00006 (Box 6)